Right now in Raju's restaurant, chappal chappal
bazaar,
daughter's marriage is going on,
hello,
fawa
ji, be
happy, be happy, where are you sitting, get up,
why are you
cooking, Didiya's sister-in-law's breakfast, Didiya's brother-in-law is cooking
breakfast,
Didiya's brother-in-law is cooking breakfast, yes, yes,
listen, I
beat you and gave
breakfast to your brother-in-law, so I forgot that how much work do I have to do, get
up and prepare the breakfast,
yes, tell me first, tell me how much, then how much,
I will tell you, then the other one will do,
but I did not say anything, I will get married, get married,
yes,
I will take the letter,
I will be
happy, I told you that you should stay in the study, stay in the study, stay in the study, stay in the study, stay in the study, stay in the study, stay in the study, stay in the study, stay in the study, stay in the study, stay in the study, stay in the study, stay in the study, stay in the study, stay in the study, stay in the study, stay in the study, stay in the study, stay in the study, stay in the study, don't be
greedy,
crazy, listen to your mind, open
your house, when your doubts are gone, then I am such a man, do
n't see
how
broken shoes are
repaired, it is a
mistake  What
mistake did I make, it is the responsibility of the
man of the house, don't talk about the male caste, don't talk about the scoundrel
man,
I
go and apply
sindoor, if you give it to me like this, then it is okay, if you take it,
then it is okay, I will separate myself, oh no, okay, put on another video, wait, take the
milk, don't eat hot milk, feed them, go and what will happen, Dada, I will immediately call myself son-in-law, I will say when will I sing a song, but if you don't give it to me, then say that the old lady is nasty, oh when are you meeting me, then I will say,
oh make Kharia, then take it, then make
milk, I don't want to
eat
kheer, make an oath, get a
sewing machine for college, or am I
too scared today, so get it
cut, spend that much money on
registration
in college, then only take the video,
take the mobile, talk,
take the mobile, if
yes, I am
on the line, then
you
want a mobile, then give it to everyone
[nasal voice] do
n't cry,
man, in the nose, in the ears, a
man gives mobile to people, I am fond of showing my face, I
say, I am
completely crazy, I am brought up, Dada, I do
n't understand  Who are we, son-in-law, how can we take my
dick around the village again? Kill me,
son-in-law, my mother is picking up things, she
says, at least
leave me alone, let's see where I come from,
or go to the market, don't let me get
upset, let me go, oh hey
Sure,
don't do it in 101 days on the day of village roaming, oh whatever you
say, tell me, while roaming the village, see
where, then
listen, do as much work as you can, if it gets bad
then marry me
[nasal voice] it's a
good thing, yes, it's okay,
take it,
don't do it in 101 days, oh I am
restless during the month of Phaaggun,
Mummy ji, please
make rotis
[sound of clearing throat]
give me respect,
take some vegetables,
where will I get something for myself, if
I do
MBS, then concentrate on studies,
think and
tell yourself,
Didi ji, I will not do it for so many hours,
but pay attention, pay attention  Damari
how am
I
useless,
after two songs if
you don't sing then you don't work,
listen to me,
you earn,
one thing mummy ji,
take it now,
after work there is a
lot, I have to do something,
okay, come on I am
stubborn, tell me, I will study in 15 days, I have to
sleep, I am like a needle in my fist, I will
earn, let's earn,
tell me the same thing,
explain my sorrow, one sorrow, one work, after
listening to this, I will ask for a loan, I am
not getting it, I will not get it by going there, it is
very difficult to go to school,
I am late, work
madam, be happy,
I am late, college opens early, think about it, are you
married, keva keva keva, yes, yes,
why does your husband keep calling so much, ca
n't you tell me, without me, I want to
sing like this, without marriage,
okay, come on, study well, you are studying well,
yes, Sapna madam,
why do you want a job,
nurse,
okay, you won't do Bihar Police,
no, Bihar Police can be done but
They are saying that you will go to Bihar Police,
then tell them that go and join Bihar Police,
after a month or four months,
how will we live? It is
better that you do B.Ed.
After that, what do you say, become a teacher,
no, do ITI, or a
nursing fellow, I think,
okay, then study hard, you will get a job in anything, if
someone in the family falls ill, I will take injections, okay, the nurse's condition is
terrible, do
n't drink alcohol,
tell them, you go to the black market, you
don't go by cycle, you get a Chhavati to go by cycle, you have a
cycle, if the chain breaks, then get your husband to
buy a scooter,
yes, if you get the payment, then buy a scooter, what should
this servant do, he is a
mechanic, he is a
good mechanic,
okay, okay, then you will get the money, you do
n't come to study, you say
that you will not get the money, come on, why are you running, come
with me, madam ji, if you catch him,
chase him away, oh, take out the thrashing and
beat him, what should I do, yes, you fight a lot, what should I do, what should I do, what should I do  Is there
anything
I know, it is difficult in the village, don't you
want to get married to your father-in-law, why don't you get married in the market, go to the market and
kill him in the middle of the market,
how does your mind bend, I
explained so much, it is
not a day now, I got it done,
okay, what are you doing, you
bastard, I would have pacified all of you, I am
also in Phagun, don't you have any
status, you are giving the stuff, bed, mat, broom, you are demanding
money, that is why you went to the
market and got
married, should I listen, did you understand
anything, oh,
I understand, what is your intelligence,
go and do drama again in the market,
yes,
go to the market and kill your
father-in-law, don't
go and kill him, keep
quiet,
but pull the scarf, give me your back, you are
pulling my life and money, when the
man is pulling your head,
tell me
Akash, I am
also useful,
you keep quiet,
I will talk, I will ask you, there is
happiness in the deposit, I will give
Rs. 100 in loan,
I lied, keep quiet,
I
swear, take four to five months of Phagun,
tell me one thing, right now when you are going to return
home,
okay, tell me the time in advance  First of all, before opening the grave, when you climb up and shout, then why do
n't you trust me, when did you come?
Well, don't worry, for now, let's just
go and leave. We are in
pain in the cup. Mehraru, we are
mad without understanding. If you don't agree after
explaining, then don't agree
without getting the day washed, don't let us wash it. What else do you do, O
[ __ ], oh oh [ __ ], I would have
washed it,
wait, come right now, Babu.  Kurwa would have
washed all these things
in the searcher's bag of the day, I wouldn't have searched for the keys in the bag, O
mother of Basa,
where should I keep ours, we would have got a lot of
everything, yes, take it, take it in the branch,
we should go, take it, you should put it
in Letiya,
go and take the
vegetables of the body, sell it in gravel, take the money
filled with Paisali,
where should I leave the money in the money, take it from me,
oh, who are you keeping ₹ 500 in the whole?  Please
give ₹500 once  If you give it as a gift in the market then
Babu should give it to me oh hey I have got the
money
now if I ask for
money then I should say it by getting angry I am
not saying it to Bhabhi
then I should explain it to you at least
explain it to you
now what should I do I don't know what to do with the husband and the
mind like I am
telling you a line of such a video that what should I give you for the night then I should say do
n't talk to him then I keep talking
dirty to
him
one day sir,
count the money to his mother in law then their brother in law will tell him the other guy
who is aunt
yes aunt after
drying the day take the
onion and take the money
from the beggar if you ask for a lot of money then give it to me take the
money
wait and take it then I will be fine
I am telling
my husband what should you do don't get registered
but after getting registered I will take it oh take
something don't roam around
in the market all
night friend
ask me yes no at
home
be happy that I am so interested in studying
[with nose  [Voice from leaving] I should ask you, you may
become a doctor or a police inspector,
but I am a son-in-law, oh I should tell you that I cannot
study peacefully, it is better to sing it, come and go, if you
believe me, then later I will
leave my studies and get a job, I have to study so much from the beginning, then you should
believe me, I am just for business,
but what can I say, such a scoundrel, he abuses me with filthy language, I have to
tolerate it by listening to it with my ears, please
write down your helplessness, show the answer on the copy, what is called adaptation, you are
writing, just write and you did
not even prepare your homework yesterday, I saw yesterday that
your copy was
late, ma'am, whenever I see you, you are always giving
percentages,
write,
why are you talking, you are
not talking to the boy, ma'am,
and where has your pen gone?  Sir,
where is your pen?   The
pen was not left.   He does
n't bring a pen.  Who knows what everyone
comes to school to do.
Where is the outfit?
What do you guys bring from home?  I do
n't have to read or write anything.   Ca
n't find it.  Done.  Done.  Hey,
why do you always make boys after seeing fairs?
Where are you taking it and making it?  Am I saying
that
you are reading a book?   If you do
n't want to read it then
write it, I have seen it on the board.  I can't see
you.  He fights with empty mouth.   He has
left, madam.
You guys drop me off every day.  People,
madam ji, no
madam ji, you people do not get money.   The
government does not give you money.
You just keep fighting with empty mouths.  be relaxed.   Do you
fight with empty mouths?
be relaxed.  Let me read it.  If you are studying then what
is your name?  Tell me this.
Rahul Kumar.   If they
cut you black then go home and sit.   Do
n't argue with mom and dad.   I will get
admission in school.
Yes.  So this is what you people have, it's not something.
Madam ji said that if I had kept the day of Gawana then I would have got
leave for one month or else I would
not have got any leave.  Okay, right?  If you get leave then it will
not be yours.  Hajri will not be possible.  So make an error,
no, who will get the application caught, who will get it caught,
write the application and give it to the Principal for a month,
yes, then write it and give it to him,
we will not talk to him, they scold us a lot,
you just tell them, it is like this with
your people, that is why we
scold them, they will
write it down and give it to me, whether you
give it or not, read what is written on the board,
answer it and give it to me quickly, okay and
you, why are you just looking at the girl's face
?   Are
?  We had told this yesterday and had
shown the questions in ours then.  Look, someone is calling.  You come with a
phone.
That's my husband calling.  There is some work.
Husband, tell your husband that we will
talk after reaching home.  Correct.  Don't bring a big phone to college.
Wait, ma'am.  Hi.
Hi.
Hi.   You are
calling, right?  I am in college,
degree in college,
madam ji, I have made a question in the market,
talk to me later, I am
writing, I am
studying in college, I am getting hit so much that I get an idea,
tell me I keep hitting F on F, I keep hitting F on F, what should I do,
listen to this, this is a lot of MBBS
studies,
beating me, I am in college, I am covered in life,
before singing, I remembered that the man is selfish, he does
n't look at me a
lot,
you come to fight,
Revad [screaming voice]
madam madam, then
who is the man,
why is he the husband?
So where is it?
Why?
Why not madam?  We Mehran, our family,
tell us
politely and quietly,
who are we studying?
Where did you study?  Where did you go after studying?  Where are you
madam ji, who should I
get a degree from?  what hey, who got a degree, who
got a degree [screaming voice]
first tell me about studies, what is the dream of a
job, make
men do useless work, if we have a dream then
I will beat you,
listen
whatever drama you want to do, go home and
be quiet, I will not tell you, this is
my family, we will beat you, we will do something
here, if you beat us, if we make a
mistake, we will beat you, don't talk
less,
come and bring it, it is
not madam's, it is
madam's, it is not all this, she is a
son or a daughter, don't tell me here, I feel like joining
another school, people are scared
here every time I see them,
what is her name, what is her
name, her name is
Priya, we are
going to beat her, first
sit here, we are coming,
rogue,
so we will talk at night, sleep, sleep
[screaming voice] hey, beat me,
we should study in college, I
mean, we should
study
together, since
before, we have been
in school, we have beaten in the market, so
we will
not talk, after we turn
I am improving improving my love [laughs]
I am okay so all the lafwa milne
re la
Akka ji I am
in school,
I have invested money in school, I have invested a lot of power,
listen to me,
these days son, I live in
peace, I
go to Raju's restaurant,
call slippers and slippers in the market, my
daughter's fate is ruined, I am not a
family,
madam, please skin me, I
sit among four boys, I study, I get
treatment, first
five marks, I get
good,
oh
today's
news, oh so it's not my
fault, it's not my love, or the
other one,
yes, then get well, go and
meet me, what are you
saying, that I have found a marriage so badly, I
have complaints, everyone in four houses, that the man
comes and beats me,
I beat the girl in the same market, I live in shame